Papers of the International Labor Defense on Microfilm 5815 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 0883. Box 10/Folder c171. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 87 pages., 1933; 33 (Reel 9)
- 0001. Box 10/Folder c172. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 94 pages., 1933; 1 (Reel 10)
  July-September 1933.
- 0095. Box 10/Folder c173. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 40 pages., 1933; 2 (Reel 10)
  October-December 1933
- 0135. Box 10/Folder c174. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 72 pages., 1934; 3 (Reel 10)
  January-April 1934
- 0207. Box 10/Folder c175. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 83 pages., 1934; 4 (Reel 10)
  May-December 1934.
- 0290. Box 10/Folder c176. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 93 pages., 1935; 5 (Reel 10)
- 0383. Box 10/Folder c177. Scottsboro case. Press Release. 80 pages., 1936-1939; 6 (Reel 10)
- 0463. Box 10/Folder c178. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 32 pages., 1933; 7 (Reel 10)
- 0495. Box 10/Folder c179. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 43 pages., 1933; 8 (Reel 10)
  April 1933 (1)
- 0538. Box 10/Folder c180. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 26 pages., 1933; 9 (Reel 10)
  April 1933 (2)
- 0564. Box 10/Folder c181. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 58 pages., 1933; 10 (Reel 10)
  April 1933 (3)
- 0622. Box 11/Folder c182. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 66 pages., 1933; 11 (Reel 10)
  May-July [October] 1933
- 0688. Box 11/Folder c183. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 36 pages., 1933; 12 (Reel 10)
  November 1933
- 0744. Box 11/Folder c184. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 69 pages., 1933; 13 (Reel 10)
  December 1933
- 0813. Box 11/Folder c185. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 38 pages., 1936; 14 (Reel 10)
  January 1936 (1)
- 0851. Box 11/Folder c186. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 62 pages., 1936; 15 (Reel 10)
  January 1936 (2)
- 0913. Box 11/Folder c187. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 42 pages., 1936; 16 (Reel 10)
  February 1936
- 0001. Box 11/Folder c188. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Daily Worker. 27 pages., 1936; 1 (Reel 11)
  March-July 1936
- 0028. Box 11/Folder c189. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Daily News. 40 pages., 1933; 2 (Reel 11)
- 0068. Box 11/Folder c190. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Daily News. 24 pages., 1933; 3 (Reel 11)
  November-December 1933
- 0092. Box 11/Folder c191. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Daily News. 8 pages., 1935-1936; 4 (Reel 11)
  November 1935- February 1936
- 0100. Box 11/Folder c192. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Journal American. 23 pages., 1933; 5 (Reel 11)
- 0123. Box 11/Folder c193. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Journal American. 6 pages., 1933; 6 (Reel 11)
- 0129. Box 11/Folder c194. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Herald Tribune. 34 pages., 1933; 7 (Reel 11)
  March-May 1933.
- 0163. Box 11/Folder c195. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Herald Tribune. 17 pages., 1933; 8 (Reel 11)
  November-December 1933.
- 0180. Box 11/Folder c196. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Mirror. 14 pages., 1933; 9 (Reel 11)
  March-June 1933.
- 0194. Box 11/Folder c197. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Mirror. 12 pages., 1933; 10 (Reel 11)
- 0206. Box 11/Folder c198. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Post. 18 pages., 1933; 11 (Reel 11)
  March-December 1933.
- 0224. Box 11/Folder c199. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Post. 19 pages., 1935-1936; 12 (Reel 11)
  November 1935- February 1936.
- 0243. Box 11/Folder c200. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Sun. 8 pages., 1933; 13 (Reel 11)
- 0251. Box 11/Folder c201. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Sun. 2 pages., 1935-1936; 14 (Reel 11)
  November 1935-February 1936.
- 0253. Box 12/Folder c202. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Times. 84 pages., 1933; 15 (Reel 11)
  March-April 1933
- 0337. Box 12/Folder c203. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - Times. 30 pages., 1935-1936; 16 (Reel 11)
- 0367. Box 12/Folder c204. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - World Telegram. 34 pages., 1933; 17 (Reel 11)
  March-October 1933.
- 0401. Box 12/Folder c205. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - World Telegram [and Times]. 44 pages., 1933; 18 (Reel 11)
- 0445. Box 12/Folder c206. Scottsboro case. News clippings: New York Press - World Telegram. 5 pages., 1935-1936; 19 (Reel 11)
  November 1935-February 1936
- 0450. Box 12/Folder c207. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Birmingham Age/Herald. 12 pages., 1933; 20 (Reel 11)
- 0462. Box 12/Folder c208. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Birmingham Age/Herald. 28 pages., 1933; 21 (Reel 11)
- 0490. Box 12/Folder c209. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Birmingham Age/Herald. 12 pages., 1935-1936; 22 (Reel 11)
- 0492. Box 12/Folder c210. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Birmingham News. 28 pages., 1933; 23 (Reel 11)
- 0520. Box 12/Folder c211. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Birmingham News. 8 pages., 1933; 24 (Reel 11)
- 0528. Box 12/Folder c212. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Birmingham News. 3 pages., 1935-1936; 25 (Reel 11)
  November 1935-March 1936
- 0531. Box 12/Folder c213. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Birmingham Post. 5 pages., 1933; 26 (Reel 11)
- 0536. Box 12/Folder c214. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Birmingham Post. 22 pages., 1933; 27 (Reel 11)
- 0558. Box 12/Folder c215. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Birmingham Post. 5 pages., 1935-1936; 28 (Reel 11)
- 0563. Box 12/Folder c216. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Decatur Daily. 75 pages., 1933; 29 (Reel 11)
  February-December 1933
- 0638. Box 12/Folder c217. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Decatur Daily. 13 pages., 1933; 30 (Reel 11)
- 0651. Box 12/Folder c218. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Decatur Daily. 7 pages., 1935-1936; 31 (Reel 11)
- 0658. Box 12/Folder c220. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Jackson County Sentinel. 49 pages., 1933; 32 (Reel 11)
  February-July 1933.
- 0707. Box 12/Folder c219. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Huntsville Times. 38 pages., 1933; 33 (Reel 11)
- 0745. Box 12/Folder c221. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Jackson County Sentinel. 4 pages., 1933; 34 (Reel 11)
- 0749. Box 12/Folder c222. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Jackson County Sentinel. 19 pages., 1935-1936; 35 (Reel 11)
  November 1935-April 1936.
- 0768. Box 12/Folder c223. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Montgomery Advertiser. 6 pages., 1933; 36 (Reel 11)
- 0774. Box 12/Folder c224. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Montgomery Advertiser. 13 pages., 1933; 37 (Reel 11)
- 0787. Box 12/Folder c225. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Montgomery Advertiser. 5 pages., 1935-1936; 38 (Reel 11)
- 0792. Box 12/Folder c226. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Miscellaneous. 9 pages., 1933; 39 (Reel 11)
- 0801. Box 12/Folder c227. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Southern Press - Miscellaneous. 12 pages., 1935-1936; 40 (Reel 11)
  November 1935-March 1936.
- 0813. Box 12/Folder c228. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Magazines: The Nation. 4 pages., 1934; 41 (Reel 11)
- 0817. Box 12/Folder c229. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Magazines - Miscellaneous. 28 pages., 1935-1936; 42 (Reel 11)
  November 1935- April 1936.
- 0845. Box 12/Folder c230. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Graves, John Temple (Seriatim). 17 pages., 1931-1934; 43 (Reel 11)
- 0862. Box 12/Folder c231. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Afro-American. 76 pages., 1933; 44 (Reel 11)
  March-September 1933
- 0001. Box 13/Folder c232. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Afro-American. 8 pages., 1936; 1 (Reel 12)
  October-December 1936
- 0009. Box 13/Folder c233. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Afro-American. 10 pages., 1935-1936; 2 (Reel 12)
- 0019. Box 13/Folder c234. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Birmingham Reporter. 20 pages., 1933; 3 (Reel 12)
  March-September 1933.
- 0039. Box 13/Folder c235. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Boston Guardian. 35 pages., 1933; 4 (Reel 12)
- 0074. Box 13/Folder c236. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Boston Guardian. 2 pages., 1933; 5 (Reel 12)
- 0076. Box 13/Folder c237. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Boston Guardian. 2 pages., 1935-1936; 6 (Reel 12)
- 0078. Box 13/Folder c238. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Chattanooga Defender. 20 pages., 1933; 7 (Reel 12)
- 0098. Box 13/Folder c239. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Chicago Defender. 44 pages., 1933; 8 (Reel 12)
- 0142. Box 13/Folder c240. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Chicago Defender. 13 pages., 1933; 9 (Reel 12)
  October-December 1933.
- 0155. Box 13/Folder c241. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Chicago Defender. 10 pages., 1935-1936; 10 (Reel 12)
- 0165. Box 13/Folder c242. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - New York Age. 38 pages., 1933; 11 (Reel 12)
- 0203. Box 13/Folder c243. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - New York Age. 5 pages., 1933; 12 (Reel 12)
- 0208. Box 13/Folder c244. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - New York Age. 9 pages., 1935-1936; 13 (Reel 12)
- 0217. Box 13/Folder c245. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - New York Amsterdam News. 51 pages., 1933; 14 (Reel 12)
- 0268. Box 13/Folder c246. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - New York Amsterdam News. 16 pages., 1933; 15 (Reel 12)
- 0284. Box 13/Folder c247. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - New York Amsterdam News. 9 pages., 1935-1936; 16 (Reel 12)
- 0293. Box 13/Folder c248. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Norfolk Journal and Guide. 39 pages., 1933; 17 (Reel 12)
- 0332. Box 13/Folder c249. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Norfolk Journal and Guide. 4 pages., 1933; 18 (Reel 12)
- 0336. Box 13/Folder c250. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Norfolk Journal and Guide. 15 pages., 1935-1936; 19 (Reel 12)
- 0351. Box 13/Folder c251. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Philadelphia Tribune. 38 pages., 1933; 20 (Reel 12)
- 0389. Box 13/Folder c252. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Philadelphia Tribune. 2 pages., 1933; 21 (Reel 12)
- 0391. Box 13/Folder c253. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Philadelphia Tribune. 3 pages., 1935-1936; 22 (Reel 12)
- 0394. Box 13/Folder c254. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Pittsburgh Courier. 56 pages., 1933; 23 (Reel 12)
- 0450. Box 13/Folder c255. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Pittsburgh Courier. 5 pages., 1933; 24 (Reel 12)
- 0455. Box 13/Folder c256. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Pittsburgh Courier. 14 pages., 1935-1936; 25 (Reel 12)
- 0469. Box 13/Folder c257. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Richmond Planet. 21 pages., 1933; 26 (Reel 12)
- 0490. Box 13/Folder c258. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Richmond Planet. 2 pages., 1933; 27 (Reel 12)
- 0492. Box 13/Folder c259. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Richmond Planet. 3 pages., 1935-1936; 28 (Reel 12)
- 0495. Box 13/Folder c260. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Washington Tribune. 23 pages., 1933; 29 (Reel 12)
- 0518. Box 13/Folder c261. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Washington Tribune. 4 pages., 1933; 30 (Reel 12)
- 0522. Box 13/Folder c262. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Washington Tribune. 8 pages., 1935-1936; 31 (Reel 12)
- 0530. Box 14/Folder c263. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (New York and Eastern). 26 pages., 1933; 32 (Reel 12)
- 0556. Box 14/Folder c264. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (New York and Eastern). 7 pages., 1933; 33 (Reel 12)
- 0563. Box 14/Folder c265. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (New York and Eastern). 10 pages., 1935-1936; 34 (Reel 12)
- 0573. Box 14/Folder c266. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (Southern). 94 pages., 1933; 35 (Reel 12)
- 0667. Box 14/Folder c267. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (Southern). 7 pages., 1933; 36 (Reel 12)
- 0674. Box 14/Folder c268. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (Southern). 14 pages., 1935-1936; 37 (Reel 12)
- 0688. Box 14/Folder c269. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (Midwestern). 83 pages., 1933; 38 (Reel 12)
- 0771. Box 14/Folder c270. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (Midwestern). 7 pages., 1933; 39 (Reel 12)
- 0778. Box 14/Folder c271. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (Midwestern). 20 pages., 1935-1936; 40 (Reel 12)
- 0798. Box 14/Folder c272. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (Western). 43 pages., 1933; 41 (Reel 12)
- 0841. Box 14/Folder c273. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (Western). 2 pages., 1933; 42 (Reel 12)
- 0843. Box 14/Folder c274. Scottsboro case. News clippings: Negro Press - Miscellaneous (Western). 8 pages., 1935-1936; 43 (Reel 12)
- 0001. Box 14. Scottsboro case. A Motion Picture Project for Scottsboro Boys Defense Fund, Proposed by Floyd C. Covington, Los Angeles, California, Urban League. 14 pages., 1933; 1 (Reel 13)
  May 15, 1933.
- 0015. Box 14. Scottsboro case. Some Facts on the Scottsboro Case, Prepared by Milton Howard, Labor Research Association. 30 pages., 1932; 2 (Reel 13)
  January 15, 1932
- 0045. Box 14. Scottsboro case. Report on the Scottsboro, Alabama Case, by Hollace Ransdell, American Civil Liberties Union. 23 pages., 1931; 3 (Reel 13)
  May 27, 1931.
- 0068. Box 14. Scottsboro case. Opinion of Judge James E. Horton of the Alabama Circuit Court Granting a Motion for a New Trial in the Scottsboro Case, by the American Civil Liberties Union. 18 pages., 1933; 4 (Reel 13)
- 0086. Box 14. Scottsboro case. Citations from Decisions from the Opinion of Judge James E. Horton of the Alabama Circuit Court Granting a Motion for a New Trial in Alabama v. Patterson. 6 pages., 1933; 5 (Reel 13)
  June 22, 1933
- 0092. Box 14. Scottsboro case. Chronology of the Scottsboro Case, by the International Labor Defense Press Service. 13 pages., 1931-1934; 6 (Reel 13)
  March 26, 1931-March 17, 1934
- 0105. Box 14. Scottsboro case. International Labor Defense National Office, Organization Department, Organization Letters and Press releases regarding the Scottsboro Case. 101 pages., 1932-1935; 7 (Reel 13)
- 0206. Box 15/Folder d1. Tom Mooney Case - General. 14 pages., 1931; 8 (Reel 13)
- 0220. Box 15/Folder d2. Tom Mooney Case - General. 24 pages., 1931-1932; 9 (Reel 13)
- 0244. Box 15/Folder d3. Tom Mooney Case - General. 12 pages., 1932; 10 (Reel 13)
- 0256. Box 15/Folder d4. Tom Mooney Case - General. 24 pages., 1933; 11 (Reel 13)
- 0280. Box 15/Folder d5. Tom Mooney Case - Trial. 116 pages., 1933; 12 (Reel 13)
  January-April 1933.
- 0281. Box 15/Folder d5. Tom Mooney Case - Trial. "My Name is Wesley Robert Wells," published by the San Francisco Civil Rights Congress. 18 pages., 1951; 13 (Reel 13)
- 0396. Box 15/Folder d6. Tom Mooney Case - Trial. 96 pages., 1933; 14 (Reel 13)
  May-December 1933.
- 0477. Box 15/Folder d6. Tom Mooney Case - Judge Louis H. Ward's Statement regarding the Tom Mooney Case. 15 pages., 1933; 15 (Reel 13)
  April 17, 1933
- 0492. Box 15/Folder d7. Tom Mooney Case - General. 116 pages., 1933-1934; 16 (Reel 13)
  [1933-] 1934
- 0608. Box 15/Folder d8. Tom Mooney Case - General. 101 pages., 1935; 17 (Reel 13)
- 0709. Box 15/Folder d9. Tom Mooney Case - A.R. Newhoff (International Labor Defense National Organizer). 74 pages., 1935; 18 (Reel 13)
- 0783. Box 15/Folder d10. Tom Mooney Case - General. 83 pages., 1936; 19 (Reel 13)
- 0001. Box 15/Folder d11. Tom Mooney Case - Correspondence. 119 pages., 1936-1938; 1 (Reel 14)
- 0120. Box 15/Folder d12. Tom Mooney Case - General. 121 pages., 1937; 2 (Reel 14)
  1937(1)
- 0241. Box 15/Folder d13. Tom Mooney Case - General. 94 pages., 1937; 3 (Reel 14)
  1937 (2)
- 0335. Box 15/Folder d14. Tom Mooney Case - General. 88 pages., 1937; 4 (Reel 14)
  1937 (3)
- 0423. Box 15/Folder d15. Tom Mooney Case - Madison Square Garden Meeting. 85 pages., 1937; 5 (Reel 14)
- 0508. Box 15/Folder d16. Tom Mooney Case - Molder's Defense Committee. 46 pages., 1937; 6 (Reel 14)
- 0554. Box 16/Folder d17. Tom Mooney Case - Molders' Defense Committee (continued). 47 pages., 1937; 7 (Reel 14)
- 0601. Box 16/Folder d18. Tom Mooney Case - Molders' Defense Committee (continued). 58 pages., 1937; 8 (Reel 14)
- 0659. Box 16/Folder d19. Tom Mooney Case - Publicity. 21 pages., 1937; 9 (Reel 14)
- 0680. Box 16/Folder d20. Tom Mooney Case - General. 58 pages., 1938; 10 (Reel 14)
- 0738. Box 16/Folder d21. Tom Mooney Case - General. 75 pages., 1938; 11 (Reel 14)
- 0813. Box 16/Folder d22. Tom Mooney Case - General. 51 pages., 1938; 12 (Reel 14)
- 0864. Box 16/Folder d23. Tom Mooney Case - General. 49 pages., 1938; 13 (Reel 14)
- 0001. Box 16/Folder d24. Tom Mooney Case - General. 78 pages., 1938; 1 (Reel 15)
- 0079. Box 16/Folder d25. Tom Mooney Case - Correspondence. 78 pages., 1938; 2 (Reel 15)
- 0157. Box 16/Folder d26. Tom Mooney Case - Correspondence: Direct Correspondence with Tom Mooney. 28 pages., 1938; 3 (Reel 15)
- 0185. Box 16/Folder d27. Tom Mooney Case - Distributed and Mimeographed Material. 20 pages., 1938; 4 (Reel 15)
- 0205. Box 16/Folder d28. Tom Mooney Case - General. 60 pages., 1939; 5 (Reel 15)
- 0265. Box 16/Folder d29. Tom Mooney Case - General. 57 pages., 1939; 6 (Reel 15)
- 0322. Box 16/Folder d30. Tom Mooney Case - General. 103 pages., 1939; 7 (Reel 15)
- 0425. Box 16/Folder d31. Tom Mooney Case - General. 49 pages., 1933-1939; 8 (Reel 15)
- 0474. Box 16/Folder d32. Tom Mooney Case - News clippings. 64 pages., 1933-1939; 9 (Reel 15)
- 0538. Box 16/Folder d33. Tom Mooney Case - Pamphlets. 216 pages., 1930-1938; 10 (Reel 15)
  [1930-1938 and Undated]
- 0646. Box 16/Folder d33. Tom Mooney Case - Pamphlets: "The C.S. Case against Labor: the Story of the Sacramento, California, Criminal Syndicalism Railroading," by Michael Quin, International Labor Defense. 17 pages., 1935; 11 (Reel 15)
  November 1935
- 0754. Box 16/Folder d35. 0646. Box 16/Folder d33. Tom Mooney Case - Warren K. Bill. 26 pages., 1939; 12 (Reel 15)
- 0780. Box 17/Folder e1. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. News clippings - Miscellaneous. 26 pages., 1933; 13 (Reel 15)
- 0806. Box 17/Folder e2. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. News clippings - Gallup Independent. 13 pages., 1933-1936; 14 (Reel 15)
  September 1933-February 1936
- 0819. Box 17/Folder e3. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Letters, Telegrams, Press Releases. 18 pages., 1933; 15 (Reel 15)
  September-November 1933
- 0837. Box 17/Folder e4. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Editorials. 7 pages., 1935; 16 (Reel 15)
- 0844. Box 17/Folder e5. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Letters, Telegrams, Press releases - 1935 Riot. 20 pages., 17 (Reel 15)
  April 5-May 2, 1935.
- 0864. Box 17/Folder e6. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. News clippings. 57 pages., 1935; 18 (Reel 15)
  March-May 1935
- 0921. Box 17/Folder e7. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Magazine Articles. 48 pages., 1935; 19 (Reel 15)
  May-November 1935
- 0001. Box 17/Folder e8. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Gallup Defense Bulletin - Gallup Defense Committee. 74 pages., 1935; 1 (Reel 16)
  April- October 1935
- 0075. Box 17/Folder e9. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. News clippings - Trade Union News. 17 pages., 1935-1936; 2 (Reel 16)
- 0092. Box 17/Folder e10. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. News clippings - Kidnapping of David Levinson and Robert Minor. 58 pages., 1935; 3 (Reel 16)
- 0160. Box 17/Folder e11. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Letters, Telegrams, Resolutions, Articles, etcetera: Kidnapping of David Levinson and Robert Minor. 90 pages., 1935; 4 (Reel 16)
- 0233. Box 17/Folder e11. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. In the Matter of an application on Behalf of David Levinson and Robert Minor for an Investigation and Prosecution by the United States of Certain Crimes against their Persons. 13 pages., 5 (Reel 16)
- 0246. Box 17/Folder e11. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. 74th Congress, 1st Session, House of Representatives, Report Number 906. 4 pages., 1935; 6 (Reel 16)
  Requesting Certain Information with Reference to alleged Kidnapping of David Levinson and Robert Minor; Communications from Department of Justice. May 14, 1935.
- 0250. Box 17/Folder e12. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Letters, Telegrams, Resolutions, Articles, etcetera. 34 pages., 1935; 7 (Reel 16)
  June- October 1935
- 0284. Box 17/Folder e13. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Letters, Telegrams, Resolutions, Articles, etcetera. 15 pages., 1935; 8 (Reel 16)
  October 4- 11, 1935
- 0299. Box 17/Folder e14. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Leaflets. 32 pages., 1935; 9 (Reel 16)
- 0331. Box 17/Folder e15. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. News clippings. 78 pages., 1935; 10 (Reel 16)
  July-October 1935
- 0409. Box 17/Folder e16. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. United American Patriots. 3 pages., 1935; 11 (Reel 16)
  September 15, 1935
- 0412. Box 17/Folder e17. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Biographies of Prisoners. 17 pages., 1935; 12 (Reel 16)
  October 7-17, 1935
- 0429. Box 17/Folder e18. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Summary of Testimony. 89 pages., 1935; 13 (Reel 16)
- 0518. Box 17/Folder e19. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Dispatches. 46 pages., 1935; 14 (Reel 16)
- 0564. Box 17/Folder e20. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Post Trial Articles, Releases, etcetera. 17 pages., 1935; 15 (Reel 16)
  October 17-November 19, 1935
- 0581. Box 17/Folder e21. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. News clippings. 27 pages., 1935-1936; 16 (Reel 16)
  November 1935- January 1936
- 0608. Box 17/Folder e22. News clippings: People's News and Union Organizer. 82 pages., 1935-1936; 17 (Reel 16)
  December 1935-March 1936
- 0690. Box 17/Folder e23. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Gallup Defense Committee - Working Folder. 25 pages., 1936; 18 (Reel 16)
- 0715. Box 17/Folder e24. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. News clippings, Leaflets, and Resolutions. 60 pages., 1936; 19 (Reel 16)
- 0775. Box 17/Folder e25. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. General. 5 pages., 1938; 20 (Reel 16)
- 0780. Box 17/Folder e26. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Manuscripts and Memoranda - General. 91 pages., 21 (Reel 16)
- 0871. Box 17. Gallup, New Mexico, Coal Mine Workers Case. Manuscripts and Memoranda - "The Gallup Miners - Martyrs for Trade Unionism," by Frank Spector and Sue Adams. 28 pages., 22 (Reel 16)
- 0899. Box 18/Folder f1. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 8 pages., 1932; 23 (Reel 16)
- 0907. Box 18/Folder f2. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 33 pages., 1933; 24 (Reel 16)
- 0940. Box 18/Folder f3. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 64 pages., 1933; 25 (Reel 16)
- 1004. Box 18/Folder f4. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings. 37 pages., 1934; 26 (Reel 16)
  March-July 1934
- 0001. Box 18/Folder f5. Angelo Herndon Case. News clippings - Bail drive. 35 pages., 1934; 1 (Reel 17)
  July-August 1934.